


general



Search



WELCOME TO YOUR SERVER, KHARNETIC!

Learn about Discord at your own pace by exploring the floating quest indicators.
Invite your friends to this server by clicking on a share button when you're ready.
Stay connected to your server from your smartphone and even use Discord while console gaming.
Reach us via our help desk or on Twitter @discordapp if you have any questions or need help.
somethingawesome - 07/26/2017
Insert helpful comment
John - 07/26/2017
List of functions
https://docs.google.com/document/d/1f91JTCYQgZhIMnxe1Qe3fmAc-iKqeTLzgUO3UM__Urk/edit?usp=sharing
Google Docs
IFB299 List of Features for Product:
IFB299 List of Features for Product: Developer: Three user types Tourist Businessman Student Administrator Each can access specific types of information with the exception of the admin who can access all and change at will. Should be a Web app which can: Display a GUI which when a user log...

Team Agreement
chrome-extension://bpmcpldpdmajfigpchkicefoigmkfalc/views/app.html
https://docs.google.com/document/d/1duk2bAelah4Htvbnll_0eax4HjVGaiuC58Vv_TnH4CU/edit?usp=sharing
Google Docs
teamagreementdefault
TEAM AGREEMENT GUIDELINES For 57 Lines Version 0.1 (DRAFT) Prepared by: Niall Stone n9731059 John Monico n9480790 Luke Humphryes n9733043 Sandali Deenalattha n9878831 Prepared for: Susan 26 July 2017 Sign-off and Approvals Team Agreement Sign-Off: The under...

July 31, 2017
Niall Stone - 07/31/2017
@here   Is there a time before the workshop wednesday that we could meet? Otherwise, we could just meet online.
Sandali_D - 07/31/2017
I'm okay with anything
I am free after 11 on Wednesday
Niall Stone - 07/31/2017
I can't do any time before the workshop on Wednesday since i have a 4 hour lecture at Kelvin grove
Sandali_D - 07/31/2017
Oh
That's fine then
somethingawesome - 07/31/2017
oh ok
Btw its important we email our tutor the Team Agreement pronto
Is it it done?
Niall Stone - 07/31/2017
Pretty sure john sent that in the workshop
somethingawesome - 07/31/2017
oh sweet
yeah i wasnt sure if someone had sent it in
Good on John then
August 2, 2017
John - 08/02/2017
https://docs.google.com/spreadsheets/d/19EN9xmpJYNW7bWSgSDNmavGIqqqev4TzAowy-RzZZIo/edit?usp=sharing
Google Docs
User Stories
Sheet1
User stories editable document
August 8, 2017
Sandali_D - 08/08/2017
Hey, did one of you guys create a repository? How do I find it?
Niall Stone - 08/08/2017
I need to add you by your Github email or username
if everyone could send those over I can send the invites
August 9, 2017
somethingawesome - 08/09/2017
GitHub username: LukeHumphryes
pardon my lateness
Niall Stone - 08/09/2017
wont be able to add until workshop
somethingawesome - 08/09/2017
np
John - 08/09/2017
https://blackboard.qut.edu.au/webapps/blackboard/execute/modulepage/viewGroup?course_id=_135147_1&group_id=_273231_1
Group 57
August 21, 2017
somethingawesome - 08/21/2017
Hi everyone, I was just wondering which set of user stories we are planning to hand in for our assessment, whether it be the ones we made in excel or Jira. Thanks
August 22, 2017
Niall Stone - 08/22/2017
I believe it'd be the ones in Jira, although since we have tomorrow's workshop we can just ask which would be better.
somethingawesome - 08/22/2017
Ok sounds like a plan
Tom.Cameron - 08/22/2017
so did we have anything to have done before class tomorrow or were we just having a look at django and stuff
somethingawesome - 08/22/2017
Well our user stories, release plan and sprint are due tomorrow before 11:59pm
Tom.Cameron - 08/22/2017
We did those all on jira/excel didnt we
do we jsut have to make into a word doc
and present it well
somethingawesome - 08/22/2017
But we have already finished the stories and the sprint
I was planning on looking  over them to see if they match the criteria
Niall Stone - 08/22/2017
pretty sure that's what we'll be doing in the workshop as well this week
somethingawesome - 08/22/2017
We can probably do the release plan during the workshop, it really isn't that complex
Ye
TBH everything is really simple
Niall Stone - 08/22/2017
yeah, we don't need to do anything new, just put what we have together mostly.
Tom.Cameron - 08/22/2017
nicela
Niall Stone - 08/22/2017
strictly speaking our first submission isn't due until week 6 anyway so ¯\_(ツ)_/¯
(since we missed out last week)
somethingawesome - 08/22/2017
Oh you're right! Sorry I didn't see that in the announcement till now
Niall Stone - 08/22/2017
So yeah, everything including the final assessment date is back 1 week.
August 27, 2017
somethingawesome - 08/27/2017
https://drive.google.com/open?id=0B8Szd261S2yCNEhQV1RkTnNuanc
Google Docs
Release Plan.docx

This is the first draft of the release plan that I've created. Please tell me if there is anything that could be improved upon. I've left the relaese dates blank for us to discuss at the next workshop. Please feel free to edit!
August 30, 2017
John - 08/30/2017
Won't be @ Uni today. For the release plan here are my details: n9480790, John Monico. Please let me know if anything happens.
somethingawesome - 08/30/2017
https://docs.google.com/document/d/1pcnUnNb-EWMEJpFMJmb-ngQ5v6oA1Pay5d7jIpkkdLo/edit?usp=sharing
Google Docs
Release Plan.docx
Release Plan Team 47 Student Number Team Member Name n9733043 Luke Humphryes Tutor: Prakash Bhandari Version: 1.0 Date: 27 Aug. 2017 Release 1 Delivery da...

somethingawesome - 08/30/2017
https://docs.google.com/document/d/1baKgZpreszLtApRNQLIy33FlLcHjR7rLZ55bRA3QGaU/edit?usp=sharing
Google Docs
Sprint Plan
Sprint Plan Sprint 1 Total Story Points:	Total Hours: Current Velocity: Story ID: Title Task ID Task Description Estimate Taken Story Points: Total Hours: Story ID: Title Task ID Task Description Estimate Taken Stor...

Niall Stone - 08/30/2017
Will be a bit late since I couldn't get out of history early.
somethingawesome - 08/30/2017
np
Tom.Cameron - 08/30/2017
Excel export is beautiful Niall
just upload it
Niall Stone - 08/30/2017
299Stories.xlsx
16.00 KB
had to add user stories manually; also moved questions/comments and acceptance criteria to their own columns
anything I need to add/change?
somethingawesome - 08/30/2017
I think refine GUI and access primary information are missing acceptance criteria. Other than that it's brilliant.
Niall Stone - 08/30/2017
yep, managed to miss those
Tom.Cameron - 08/30/2017
Excel export is beautiful Niall
just upload it
jokes but yeah that looks really nice
Niall Stone - 08/30/2017
(also changed the "fix version/s" heading to "feature category")
anyway I won't be uploading till around 8 or later so we can make any changes we think of in the meantime
but it could easily be uploaded in a couple of minutes as-is
somethingawesome - 08/30/2017
I mean I can't really see anything wrong with it currently
Great job btw
Niall Stone - 08/30/2017
so uhh.. where do you actually submit the file?
also, since I couldn't find something definitive, PDF or .DOCX on the plans?
Niall Stone - 08/30/2017
did someone already try to submit?
somethingawesome - 08/30/2017
I didnt
John - 08/30/2017
Not me. Try looking at the group section on bb. Might be a submission link there
Niall Stone - 08/30/2017
nope don't worry, I found the link
somethingawesome - 08/30/2017
Oh sorry I missed your message, docx should be fine
Niall Stone - 08/30/2017
after much being blindness
somethingawesome - 08/30/2017
Sweet
John - 08/30/2017
:thumbsup:
somethingawesome - 08/30/2017
I'd recommend downloading the file and seeing if you can view all 3 documents properly
Niall Stone - 08/30/2017
doing so now
somethingawesome - 08/30/2017
Coolski
Niall Stone - 08/30/2017
both look fine
Tom.Cameron - 08/30/2017
Good job
somethingawesome - 08/30/2017
:thumbsup:
Niall Stone - 08/30/2017
Team_57_Stories__Planning.zip
39.80 KB
can someone just make sure that's working fine?
somethingawesome - 08/30/2017
Sure can
Tom.Cameron - 08/30/2017
worked for me
Niall Stone - 08/30/2017
excellent. Submitting now then
somethingawesome - 08/30/2017
All good on my end
Ok I just downloaded it and it was all good. Nice work Niall
Niall Stone - 08/30/2017
looks like my years of education have finally paid off
Tom.Cameron - 08/30/2017
Sic
somethingawesome - 08/30/2017
About time, amarite?
Sandali_D - 08/30/2017
Great work. I'm sorry I was out today. Didn't see the msgs :neutral_face:
September 1, 2017
somethingawesome - 09/01/2017
Hey guys, this is what i came up with for the landing page. It would be great if i could get some feedback on it. Thanks.

John - 09/01/2017
Looks very professional!
Tom.Cameron - 09/01/2017
yeah looks nice af
Niall Stone - 09/01/2017
umm, yeah, that's beautiful
somethingawesome - 09/01/2017
Thanks! Is there anything you can point out that could be improved?
Tom.Cameron - 09/01/2017
forgot*
lol jks it already is
i am blind
wtf
somethingawesome - 09/01/2017
Rekt
Tom.Cameron - 09/01/2017
umm amybe if the forgot your password was centered
but it might also look shite
somethingawesome - 09/01/2017
I'll give it a cheeky centering and see how it looks
September 6, 2017
Tom.Cameron - 09/06/2017
Can't make it to class today sorry
Sandali_D - 09/06/2017
I won't be able to make it today either
Trying to finish my CAB202 assessment
somethingawesome - 09/06/2017
Yeah I did CAB202 last semester and it was pretty time consuming
John - 09/06/2017
Has anyone done and wireframe designs yet for our app? If not, I'll get started on some before class so we have something to work with.
Tom.Cameron - 09/06/2017
cab202 is messed
i was so bad at 202
somethingawesome - 09/06/2017
I haven't, I'm still working with logins n stuff
CAB202 = soooooooo bad
John - 09/06/2017
I'll do them then. Maybe also a logo
somethingawesome - 09/06/2017
https://scotch.io/tutorials/build-your-first-python-and-django-application
Scotch
Build Your First Python and Django Application
Python and Django can help make quick and functional applications.

John - 09/06/2017
https://confluence.atlassian.com/agile065/jira-agile-user-s-guide/using-the-jira-agile-gadgets/using-the-sprint-burndown-gadget
September 11, 2017
Niall Stone - 09/11/2017
https://cdn.discordapp.com/attachments/204067392018579456/356743288620974091/unknown.png

working on a Data Flow Diagram basis atm; haven't got much time to work on django-proper because migraines are fun. anything i've missed here that anyone can see?
September 12, 2017
Niall Stone - 09/12/2017
so I've got user registration working. anyone have any progress on those design documents which are due tomorrow?
somethingawesome - 09/12/2017
Did you create a registration page?
Niall Stone - 09/12/2017
yep. about to push it to the github
somethingawesome - 09/12/2017
oh ok awesome
well i reckon we can take off the create an account user story
Niall Stone - 09/12/2017

second one is new
some things aren't in there as of yet
but I only had to spend 10 minutes on actual registration functionality
most of the last 2 hours has been spent trying to get dang CSS to work
that is, an external CSS file
works now though
somethingawesome - 09/12/2017
yeah coding life amarite?
tahts great though thanks
Niall Stone - 09/12/2017
can I get whoever owns this server to give me webhook access?
somethingawesome - 09/12/2017
Im sorry
sorry?*
Niall Stone - 09/12/2017
it basically lets you send a notification to the server whenever someone makes an update on github
somethingawesome - 09/12/2017
i think john owns it
Niall Stone - 09/12/2017
dang
oh well
somethingawesome - 09/12/2017
I 100% have nothing to do with the server
Niall Stone - 09/12/2017
it's not super important or anything
it's just nice to get a notification for when people update
i'll ask john about it tomorrow
somethingawesome - 09/12/2017
on the subject of things we were supposed to complete...
i thought john drew all the UI sketches
Niall Stone - 09/12/2017
the UI sketches aren't what they were asking for
the design documents are like the data flow diagram, the component diagram
somethingawesome - 09/12/2017
Is it week 8 this week?
Niall Stone - 09/12/2017
technically I think yes
for this subject its week 7
Home Work
Before workshop 7, team must complete and upload the following artefacts to their GIT 
Repository. 
Each member should contribute in producing these artefacts. Member(s) of the 
team who have contributed in producing these artefacts to submit as their individual 
contribution(s) in personal portfolio submission for Sprint 1. Two members can work on the 
sam
e artefact if required but will need to demonstrate their individual contribution in the 
personal portfolio submission.
1.
Justification for selecting a specific architecture pattern for Smart City project
2.
Logical and Physical diagrams of the chosen architect
ure pattern for Smart City project
3.
Component
 Diagram for Smart City project
4.
Data Flow Diagram
 for Smart City project
somethingawesome - 09/12/2017
ok so what have we got?
Niall Stone - 09/12/2017
I've done the Data Flow Diagram since I did those before
afaik nothing else
somethingawesome - 09/12/2017
dont we have the Logical and Physical diagrams done?
Sandali_D - 09/12/2017
I'll do the component diagram
Niall Stone - 09/12/2017
I mean if we do that'd be nice
I gotta be off for a bit; see if you can work something out
September 13, 2017
John - 09/13/2017
I don't own the server Naill. Won't be at the tutorial this afternoon. If you guys have uploaded to github I'll be able to work from from home for a few hours but have to goto a function at 3p.m. . Let me know we need anything specific. from me.
Sandali_D - 09/13/2017
What is the architecture pattern selected
I'll draw the logical and physical diagrams
But I should know the architecture pattern first
Sandali_D - 09/13/2017
Can anyone explain to me what a physical and a logical diagram is?
Is it like we have to draw physical DFD and logical DFD?
Sandali_D - 09/13/2017
Component_Diagram.pdf
10.85 KB
https://www.lucidchart.com/pages/data-flow-diagram/logical-vs-physical-data-flow-diagram
September 16, 2017
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
so when can everyone meet on discord for a group meeting?
Niall Stone - 09/16/2017
pretty much any time outside of day-time mon,tue,wed
all the changes I made wednesday for the registration page are up
will attempt to create a template for the main page we can fill as long as no one else is doing so
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
Oh no need I've already devised a main page. I've left the Nav bar though for Sandali. I'm sorry I missed your message, I would have replied sooner otherwise.
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
ok so i just uploaded my smartcity folder to github. If you run the server in the smart city folder than everything should work alright. If you click the login button it takes you to the main page.
Niall Stone - 09/16/2017
i'll merge your code over to the main branch and take a look then
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
I've made an account for Susan btw and an admin page
If you want to access the page just put /admin/ on the end of the websites url
Niall Stone - 09/16/2017
I can't run the server
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
Are you in the smart city folder?
Niall Stone - 09/16/2017
yep
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
Ok I'll have a look
Niall Stone - 09/16/2017

yen symbols are backslashes
don't ask
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
I've downloaded it and I can run the server
Can you see the manage.py in the smartcity folder?
Niall Stone - 09/16/2017
yes, it's the one i'm running
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
I'm quite confused then


Niall Stone - 09/16/2017
can you run my version?
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
I guess you can just use the app folders
I'll try
It's on GitHub yeah?
Niall Stone - 09/16/2017
yes
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
Just to make sure what other folders are in the smartcity one?
Niall Stone - 09/16/2017
adminpage, landingpage etc
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
So it is up to date then
Niall Stone - 09/16/2017
yes, I just merged your fork into the main repository
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
Ok I'm downloading yours now
Perhaps you need my Django file?
Niall Stone - 09/16/2017
is not your entire project in what you uploaded?
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
Yes it is
Niall Stone - 09/16/2017
then that should be all that's needed
have you tried my project?
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
Ok so I just tried it and I got this:

Niall Stone - 09/16/2017
so, everything is working except CSS
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
Is that what it's supposed to do?
Niall Stone - 09/16/2017
CSS isn't working
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
ok
Niall Stone - 09/16/2017
but the server runs?
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
great
yeah
Niall Stone - 09/16/2017
like, you're running the server right?
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
ye
Niall Stone - 09/16/2017
k, try /auth/register I think?
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
alrighty

Niall Stone - 09/16/2017
same again then
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
so just the css
ill test it to see of the logic works
Niall Stone - 09/16/2017
can you try navigating to:
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
but im not sure how id know
Niall Stone - 09/16/2017
http://127.0.0.1:8000/auth/static/mainStyle.css
(assuming that's the address you're using)
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
why dont you incorperate the css in the html file?
Niall Stone - 09/16/2017
because then you have to put it in every single HTML file
which is annoying and creates a lot of code clutter
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
yeah i guess so
but tbf its way easier
Niall Stone - 09/16/2017
well on my end putting in the CSS is a matter of 
<link rel="stylesheet" type="text/css" href="http://127.0.0.1:8000/auth/static/mainStyle.css">
and if you want to change it you only need to change it in one place
rather than everywhere
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
is that in the html file?
Niall Stone - 09/16/2017
yep
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
ok hang on a sec
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
what is the html file for the register page?
Niall Stone - 09/16/2017
'name.html'
really should get around to changing it
but not going to do that while we're dealing with this
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
and how can i register and see if it worked?
dont worry about it, function is #!
#1*
Niall Stone - 09/16/2017
if you put things in the fields and hit register, it should redirect you to a non-existent page called '/thanks/'
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
ok cool
Niall Stone - 09/16/2017
from then, you should be able to look in the database with some kind of database browser
eg. SQLite browser
if you want to confirm the SQL entry
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
ok
still no luck with running my server?
Niall Stone - 09/16/2017
just had to delete all the .pyc files and it worked again
if you want i'll try and apply the functionality to your templates since they're looking nicer
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
yeah ok as long as youre up for it
good to know you can run the server though
Niall Stone - 09/16/2017
yep. and can we start using the same repository from now on? unless you're making huge directory changes etc. it's easier to collaborate if we keep things in the same place
otherwise, just merge frequently and things should be kept nicely
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
ok sounds good, I'm new to github so if i just keep uploading my files to the repository i used for the latest smartcity file we sholud be good?
Niall Stone - 09/16/2017
sure. just send a message here when you've made a commit so I can merge it into the main branch
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
ok sure thing
hopefully i wont screw that up
Niall Stone - 09/16/2017
well i'd love to have an automatic message for that
unfortunately apparently no-one owns this server
somethingawesome - 09/16/2017
kek
i swear its not me
This is the first time ive ever used github
September 17, 2017
Sandali_D - 09/17/2017
Hey guys
Will it be okay if I change the position of the logo
It will be on top of the navigation bar
Is that okay?
Niall Stone - 09/17/2017
if you feel like it works there, go for it
Sandali_D - 09/17/2017
Okay :smile:
somethingawesome - 09/17/2017
Sounds cool
Tom.Cameron - 09/17/2017
Guys just checking that sprint 1 is finished in week 9 but week 10 for us?
or is sprint 1 due by wednesday?
Sandali_D - 09/17/2017
yeah
Not this week
its due by next week wednesday
somethingawesome - 09/17/2017
I thought we have 20 days regardless
somethingawesome - 09/17/2017
Oh no it's actually 30 days
My mistake, guess I should change the burndown chart
30 days makes more sense as to lines up with week 10
Tom.Cameron - 09/17/2017
nicela
somethingawesome - 09/17/2017
Yeah pretty sik
Legit thought it was due Wednesday
Tom.Cameron - 09/17/2017
yeah i just saw the email and was freaking for a little bit
then remembered we are a week behind
somethingawesome - 09/17/2017
Thank god for the Ekka holiday
John - 09/17/2017
:sweat_smile: :ok_hand:
September 18, 2017
somethingawesome - 09/18/2017
Ok so we now have a working database for storing the locations
ill upload my work to github
the folder/app "dbviews" is where i keep the referenced model.py and it also works as a test page for creating tables in html.
if you go 127.0.0.1:8000/dbview/ you should see this:

the data are placeholders atm obvo
So to put them in the main page we just need to copy whats in the "dbviews.html" file
although i have no idea how to format it yet :neutral_face:
Niall Stone - 09/18/2017
looks good; will take a better look when I get out of this network lecture
Sandali_D - 09/18/2017
I made the Nav bar
But I really don't know how to upload it
:neutral_face:
somethingawesome - 09/18/2017
When you are on git hub, can you see the grey tab that says upload files?
It's next to the green one that says download files
Zip folder*
This is on the website btw not the application
September 19, 2017
somethingawesome - 09/19/2017
with the burndown chart, is it 30 or 20 days?
Niall Stone - 09/19/2017
30
somethingawesome - 09/19/2017
cool and is it story points remaining or tasks?
Niall Stone - 09/19/2017
story points iirc
somethingawesome - 09/19/2017
sweet thanks
Niall Stone - 09/19/2017
@somethingawesome did you commit your changes to the github? everything's showing as last update 3 days ago
somethingawesome - 09/19/2017
I thought i had, ill try again
let me know if it comes up
Niall Stone - 09/19/2017
are you using the app? if so, you have to hit the sync button I think, to have all your changes upload
somethingawesome - 09/19/2017
yeah i just tried it and it came up with erroes
errors*
no wait i think they are just alerts
ok can you try it now?
dbview folder and admin folder should be new
Niall Stone - 09/19/2017

what are the alerts like?
somethingawesome - 09/19/2017
showing me changes
Niall Stone - 09/19/2017
and does it let you commit?
somethingawesome - 09/19/2017
have you looked at the files?
yeah
Niall Stone - 09/19/2017
the folders use the latest file's commit
have you hit sync?
somethingawesome - 09/19/2017
ok try now
Niall Stone - 09/19/2017
still getting nothing. Here, you can check and make sure i'm not just going crazy
https://github.com/LukeHumphryes/ifb299-57lines
GitHub
LukeHumphryes/ifb299-57lines
Contribute to ifb299-57lines development by creating an account on GitHub.

somethingawesome - 09/19/2017
what the hell is goin on
ok im going to do one of these
alright that should do it
Niall Stone - 09/19/2017
yep, marked as updated. was that everything uploaded?
somethingawesome - 09/19/2017
ye
Well i mean it should have been
Niall Stone - 09/19/2017
cool. I'll get to work implementing the registration & login pages
somethingawesome - 09/19/2017
awesome
This is our new and improved burndown chart btw
Burndown1.xlsx
15.47 KB
we are so close to the target points
Niall Stone - 09/19/2017
shiny, looks good
Niall Stone - 09/19/2017
in the future, please try to avoid using 'fixed' positions for everything
somethingawesome - 09/19/2017
My bad, is 'absolute' better?
Niall Stone - 09/19/2017
generally better not to use a positioning tag at all, and instead work things with relative distances so it's easier to add more fields
not that important
anyway, login and registration work again
September 20, 2017
somethingawesome - 09/20/2017
sweeeeeeet
Sandali_D - 09/20/2017
I'll commit mine today
I didn't have wifi for three days :neutral_face:
somethingawesome - 09/20/2017
btw i wouldnt recomend changing the positions that are absolute otherwise they wont move with the scroll
wow
that sucks
Sandali_D - 09/20/2017
I know :neutral_face:
somethingawesome - 09/20/2017
wifi is like a survival need for the modern age
Sandali_D - 09/20/2017
Haha yeah
All sorted now I'll commit it today
John - 09/20/2017
I'm putting together the test data we can use with our app. So far I've planned 3 examples of each. If you guys have any suggestions let me know. I'm current;y using real Australian cases.
somethingawesome - 09/20/2017
Ive done all of the libraries and colleges in brisbane
i suggest just putting in places with the 4000 postcode
John - 09/20/2017
Thats what I'm doing. I'll skip Libaries and colleges then
somethingawesome - 09/20/2017
cool
John - 09/20/2017
Hey Tom mate when you see this can you let us know where your up to in your contributions (artifacts). You should have 5 to get the best marks for yourself. If you are looking for things to do feel free to ask or check the JIRA
Same goes for anyone else who is feel slost or out of the loop!
Sandali_D - 09/20/2017
Can we use user stories as an artifact
John - 09/20/2017
Yes. Here is thepart of the FAQ that relates to that:
Used scenario and storyboarding to explore and explain client interaction with the web siteSubmit the scenarios used and corresponding storyboards. Explain how your approach improved the final design of the productInclude the description of the final product where your work is used by the team
SEE HERE FOR LIST OF ARTIFACT EXAMPLES
Frequently_asked_questions.pdf
86.51 KB
Sandali_D - 09/20/2017
Okay thanks :sweat_smile:
Can I use logical diagram and physical diagram as two artifacts
Or are they considered as one artefact
John - 09/20/2017
If your artifacts are too small they won't get you very much marks
EG I counted all four UI designs as 1 Artifact for safety
Sandali_D - 09/20/2017
Okay
So I'll take those two as one
And I'll pick another thing from JIRA
John - 09/20/2017
Everyone this is a message from the Tutor. He says that "Tutorial Attendance should be mandatory". We don't mind this week but it would be good to see everyone back here after the midsemester break as there in in-tutorial activities that are part of our assesment like todays class diagram
somethingawesome - 09/20/2017
Ok so this th new and correct(ish) burndown chart
Burndown3.xlsx
15.24 KB
Sandali_D - 09/20/2017
hey is there a way for me to access jira from home?
somethingawesome - 09/20/2017
Yes, download "Cisco vpn"
Once you have it open put in qut.edu,au
And your qut password
September 21, 2017
Sandali_D - 09/21/2017
hey guys
What is there in this sprint for me to choose
ones that are left
I need one more artefact
And i cant access JIRA
somethingawesome - 09/21/2017

Sandali_D - 09/21/2017
Thank you so much
somethingawesome - 09/21/2017
np
Sandali_D - 09/21/2017
Can I do initial data entry
somethingawesome - 09/21/2017
Sorry I forgot to mark that as resolved. John did it yesterday.
um can you access my smartcity folder on github?
Sandali_D - 09/21/2017
yeah i can
somethingawesome - 09/21/2017
if so you can use that to complete the accessing primary information story
Sandali_D - 09/21/2017
yeah ill do that
somethingawesome - 09/21/2017
awesome
Sandali_D - 09/21/2017
:sweat_smile:
somethingawesome - 09/21/2017
ive already done it for libraries and colleges
Sandali_D - 09/21/2017
So i have to do it for hotels>
somethingawesome - 09/21/2017
you can literally just copied what i did for them
oh and theyre all in the mainpage
Just do all of them for now
Sandali_D - 09/21/2017
mainpage folder?
somethingawesome - 09/21/2017
we can sort out when they appear for users later
Sandali_D - 09/21/2017
okay ill do it
so i dont have to sort it to different users
somethingawesome - 09/21/2017
mainpage/templates/mainpage.html
Sandali_D - 09/21/2017
just a general access?
somethingawesome - 09/21/2017
yep
Sandali_D - 09/21/2017
okay sure thank you so much
somethingawesome - 09/21/2017
for now anyway
Sandali_D - 09/21/2017
okay
somethingawesome - 09/21/2017
please feel free to message me if you have any questions about it
Sandali_D - 09/21/2017
okay sure thank you so much you are a life saver
:sweat_smile:
September 22, 2017
Tom.Cameron - 09/22/2017
Hey guys
sorry
for not coming to yesterdays or technically two days ago class
i know i have been a shit team member
i stayed up all nigth tuesday trying to figure out what the fuck i am doing
but idk kinda depressed atm and being a piece of shit
so like thats on me
should be good now
still kinda lost
dont having anything due for the next week besides this
so i should be able to do this
but like idk what the fuck iam doing
and i am sorry
John - 09/22/2017
Its alright. Theres plenty of time for you to get into this project during the midsem break. Take a look at Jira and the FAQ I posted and prepare for yourself 5 artifacts thtough code snippets and other contributions
Then just be there for the last 4 tuts
We are actually lucky since sprint 1 isnt due untill week 10 friday now which is 2 weeks away. A huge extension!
Tom, if you are look for some extra help with the coding there is stimulate: https://www.student.qut.edu.au/learning-and-assessment/workshops-and-academic-help/academic-help#h2-3
QUT
Academic help
One-on-one consultations and drop-in sessions to help you develop your skills and complete you assignments.

And if you need to contact the lecturer/our tutors here are thier details, They can also help you out if you are feeling really lost
Lecturer: p.bhandari@qut.edu.au
Tutor: benjamin.saljooghi@gmail.com
John - 09/22/2017
QUT also has free counselling for students that might help you out: https://www.qut.edu.au/about/services-and-facilities/all-services/student-counselling-services
QUT
Counselling services
Counselling Services helps students with personal, living, study or work related concerns.

somethingawesome - 09/22/2017
@Tom.Cameron Don't worry about it, we have the whole of the mid semester break to work on it before it's due so no need to stress yourself out.
September 29, 2017
somethingawesome - Yesterday at 10:19 PM
Hey guys is the portfolio due on Friday next week?
Niall Stone - Yesterday at 10:21 PM
si
September 30, 2017
somethingawesome - Today at 11:58 AM
cheers